Miss,
يغيب،
do you want to watch the show?
هل تريد مشاهدة العرض؟
I heard that
سمعت ان
someone came outside to deliver the edict,
خرج شخص ما لتسليم الفتوى ،
Duke Jingbei
دوق جينغبى
will be in bad luck.
سيكون في حظ سيئ.
Really?
هل حقا؟
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
Let's go and have a look.
دعنا نذهب ونلقي نظرة.
I didn't expect the wedding ceremony of the Heavenly Palace Office
لم أتوقع حفل زفاف مكتب القصر السماوي
to come so soon.
ليأتي قريبًا.
My lady, slow down.
سيدتي ، تمهل.
Wei Shangzhi, how dare you disobey the imperial edict?
Wei Shangzhi ، كيف تجرؤ على عصيان المرسوم الإمبراطوري؟
What kind of decree did you send?
ما نوع المرسوم الذي أرسلته؟
Seeing the imperial edict is like seeing His Majesty,
إن رؤية المرسوم الإمبراطوري يشبه رؤية جلالة الملك ،
This is disrespectful.
هذا غير محترم.
Dirty.
متسخ.
Be good.
كن جيد.
What about him?
ماذا عنه؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't die.
لن أموت.
Chuan Gu,
تشوان جو ،
take him away.
يأخذه بعيدا.
Yes.
نعم.
His Lordship is wise,
سيادته حكيمة ،
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Suqiu,
Suqiu ،
go and find out where the person who passed the imperial edict is?
اذهب واكتشف أين هو الشخص الذي أصدر المرسوم الإمبراطوري؟
Okay,
تمام،
Got it.
فهمتك.
I heard that the meat on both sides of a person's cheeks is the tenderest.
سمعت أن اللحم على جانبي وجنتيه هو ألطف.
His Lordship is wise.
سيادته حكيمة.
Say it or not?
قلها أم لا؟
Bah!
باه!
I'm talking about you.
انا أتحدث عنك.
Wei Shangzhi,
وي شانجزي ،
you bullied His Majesty for being young,
كنت تتنمر على جلالة الملك لكونك شابًا ،
He controls the government
يسيطر على الحكومة
and does all kinds of evil,
ويفعل كل أنواع الشر ،
Now you even dare not accept the imperial edict.
الآن أنت لا تجرؤ حتى على قبول المرسوم الإمبراطوري.
This is a great crime to be executed with the whole clan.
هذه جريمة كبرى أن يتم إعدامها مع كل العشيرة.
My lady,
سيدتي،
bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Marquis Jingbei, the man who eats human flesh and drinks human blood
ماركيز جينغبى ، الرجل الذى يأكل لحم الإنسان ويشرب دمه
to pass the imperial edict is probably in bad shape.
لتمرير المرسوم الإمبراطوري ربما يكون في حالة سيئة.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Kitchen,
مطبخ،
Let's go.
لنذهب.
How come a good person
كيف يمكن لشخص جيد
has such a long mouth
لديه مثل هذا الفم الطويل
to tell me,
ليقول لي ،
Tell me.
أخبرني.
My Lady.
سيدتي.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
Miss,
يغيب،
take a look.
إلق نظرة.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Murder! Murder!
قتل!  قتل!
Tell me,
أخبرني،
Kawaku,
كاواكو ،
throw him to the dungeon,
رميه إلى الزنزانة ،
Don't let him die.
لا تدعه يموت.
Yes.
نعم.
You may leave now.
يمكنك الانصراف الآن.
Zhi,
زي ،
come out.
يظهر.
I'm cold.
أنا بردان.
The kitchen just
المطبخ فقط
made it. Try it.
اصنعها.  جربها.
You don't like it?
لا يعجبك؟
Go away.
يبتعد.
Don't stay under the quilt.
لا تبقَ تحت اللحاف.
Don't suffocate yourself.
لا تخنق نفسك.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
I've found out everything.
لقد اكتشفت كل شيء.
The servant is locked in the dungeon.
تم حبس الخادم في الزنزانة.
I lost two pieces of meat on my face.
لقد فقدت قطعتين من اللحم على وجهي.
Is that his flesh?
أهذا لحمه؟